Guide to the Henry Noble MacCracken Papers, 1907 - circa 1968
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES III. FACULTY, 1914-1945
  - FACULTY, 1926-1928
    - Latin, 1926-1928
      - Officers (Folder 32.21)
    - Library, 1926-1928
      - Appointments (Folder 32.22)
      - Officers (Folder 32.23)
      - Officers (Folder 32.24)
    - Mathematics, 1926-1928
      - Appointments (Folder 32.25)
      - Officers (Folder 32.26)
    - Music, 1926-1928
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 32.27)
      - Appointments (Folder 32.28)
      - Conferences (Folder 32.29)
      - Officers (Folder 32.30)
      - Officers (Folder 32.31)
    - Nursery School, 1926-1928
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 32.32)
      - Appointments (Folder 32.33)
      - Conferences (Folder 32.34)
      - Conferences (Folder 32.35)
      - Officers (Folder 32.36)
      - Summer Institute of Euthenics (Folder 32.37)
    - Philosophy, 1926-1928
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 32.38)
      - Officers (Folder 32.39)
    - Physical Education, 1926-1928
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 32.40)
      - Appointments (Folder 32.41)
      - Conferences (Folder 32.42)
      - Officers (Folder 32.43)
    - Physics, 1926-1928
      - Appointments (Folder 32.44)
      - Conferences (Folder 32.45)
      - Officers (Folder 32.46)
    - Physiology, 1926-1928
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 32.47)
      - Appointments (Folder 32.48)
      - Conferences (Folder 32.49)
      - Officers (Folder 32.50)
      - Officers (Folder 32.51)
    - Political Science, 1926-1928
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 32.52)
      - Appointments (Folder 32.53)
      - Conferences (Folder 32.54)
      - Officers (Folder 32.55)
    - Psychology, 1926-1928
      - Applications (Folder 32.56)
      - Appointments (Folder 32.57)
      - Conferences (Folder 32.58)
      - Officers (Folder 32.59)
    - Religion, 1926-1928
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 32.60)
      - Appointments (Folder 32.61)
      - Conferences (Folder 32.62)
      - Officers (Folder 32.63)
    - Spanish, 1926-1928
      - Applications (Folder 32.64)
      - Appointments (Folder 32.65)
      - Conferences (Folder 32.66)
      - Officers (Folder 32.67)
    - Warden's Office, 1926-1928
      - Appointments (Folder 32.68)
      - Conferences (Folder 32.69)
      - Officers (Folder 32.70)
      - Miss Palmer (Folder 32.71)
      - Reports (Folder 32.72)
    - Zoology, 1926-1928
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 32.73)
      - Appointments (Folder 32.74)
      - Officers (Folder 32.75)
  - FACULTY, 1928-1930
    - General, 1928-1930
      - Faculty Bibliographies, 1928-1929 (Folder 33.1)
      - Faculty Bibliographies, 1929-1930 (Folder 33.2)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.3)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.4)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.5)
      - Officers (Folder 33.6)
      - Officers (Folder 33.7)
    - Astronomy, 1928-1930
      - Officers (Folder 33.8)
      - Officers (Folder 33.9)
    - Botany, 1928-1930
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.10)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.11)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.12)
      - Officers (Folder 33.13)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.14)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.15)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.16)
      - Officers (Folder 33.17)
    - Chemistry, 1928-1930
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.18)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.19)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.20)
      - Officers (Folder 33.21)
      - Officers (Folder 33.22)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.23)
    - Child Study, 1928-1930
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.24)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.25)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.26)
      - Officers (Folder 33.27)
      - Officers (Folder 33.28)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.29)
      - Officers (Folder 33.30)
    - Dean, 1928-1930
      - Committee on Admissions (Folder 33.31)
      - Answers to letters referred to Comm. on Admission (Folder 33.32)
      - Committee on Admission - minutes (Folder 33.33)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.34)
      - Officers (Folder 33.35)
      - Vocational Bureau (Folder 33.36)
      - Officers (Folder 33.37)
      - Answers to letters referred to Comm. on Admission (Folder 33.38)
      - Officers (Folder 33.39)
      - Reports (Folder 33.40)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.41)
      - Vocational Bureau (Folder 33.42)
    - Economics, 1928-1930
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.43)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.44)
      - Officers (Folder 33.45)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.46)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.47)
      - Officers (Folder 33.48)
    - English, 1928-1930
      - Appointments (Folder 33.49)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.50)
      - Officers (Folder 33.51)
      - Officers (Folder 33.52)
      - Officers (Folder 33.53)
      - Officers (Folder 33.54)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.55)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.56)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.57)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.58)
    - Euthenics, 1928-1930
      - Summer Institute (Folder 33.59)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.60)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.61)
      - Handcraft Courses (Folder 33.62)
      - Officers (Folder 33.63)
      - Officers (Folder 33.64)
      - Summer Institute (Folder 33.65)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.66)
      - Summer Institute - Progressive Association (Folder 33.67)
    - French, 1928-1930
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.68)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.69)
      - Officers (Folder 33.70)
      - Officers (Folder 33.71)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.72)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.73)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.74)
    - Geology, 1928-1930
      - Appointments (Folder 33.75)
      - Officers (Folder 33.76)
      - Officers (Folder 33.77)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.78)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.79)
    - German, 1928-1930
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.80)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.81)
      - Conference (Folder 33.82)
      - Officers (Folder 33.83)
      - Officers (Folder 33.84)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.85)
      - Appointments (Folder 33.86)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.87)
    - Greek,1928-1930
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 33.88)
      - Officers (Folder 33.89)
      - Conferences (Folder 33.90)
      - Officers (Folder 33.91)
    - History, 1928-1930
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.1)
      - Conferences (Folder 34.2)
      - Officers (Folder 34.3)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.4)
      - Officers (Folder 34.5)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.6)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.7)
      - Conferences (Folder 34.8)
    - Italian, 1928-1930
      - Officers (Folder 34.9)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.10)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.11)
      - Officers (Folder 34.12)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.13)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.14)
    - Latin, 1928-1930
      - Officers (Folder 34.15)
      - Conferences (Folder 34.16)
      - Officers (Folder 34.17)
    - Library, 1928-1930
      - Officers (Folder 34.18)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.19)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.20)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.21)
      - Conferences (Folder 34.22)
      - Officers (Folder 34.23)
    - Mathematics, 1928-1930
      - Officers (Folder 34.24)
      - Officers (Folder 34.25)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.26)
    - Music, 1928-1930
      - Officers (Folder 34.27)
      - Officers (Folder 34.28)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.29)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.30)
      - Conferences (Folder 34.31)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.32)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.33)
      - Conferences (Folder 34.34)
    - Philosophy, 1928-1930
      - Appointments (Folder 34.35)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.36)
      - Officers (Folder 34.37)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.38)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.39)
      - Officers (Folder 34.40)
    - Political Science, 1928-1930
      - Officers (Folder 34.41)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.42)
      - Officers (Folder 34.43)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.44)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.45)
    - Physics, 1928-1930
      - Officers (Folder 34.46)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.47)
      - Officers (Folder 34.48)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.49)
    - Physiology, 1928-1930
      - Conferences (Folder 34.50)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.51)
      - Officers (Folder 34.52)
      - Officers (Folder 34.53)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.54)
      - Conferences (Folder 34.55)
      - Officers - Health (Folder 34.56)
      - Appointments -Health (Folder 34.57)
      - Applications and Recommendations - Health (Folder 34.58)
      - Conferences - Health (Folder 34.59)
    - Physical Education, 1928-1930
      - Officers (Folder 34.60)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.61)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.62)
      - Conferences (Folder 34.63)
      - Officers (Folder 34.64)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.65)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.66)
      - Dalcroze Eurythmics (Folder 34.67)
    - Psychology, 1928-1930
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.68)
      - Conferences (Folder 34.69)
      - Officers (Folder 34.70)
      - Officers (Folder 34.71)
    - Religion, 1928-1930
      - Appointments (Folder 34.72)
      - Officers (Folder 34.73)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.74)
      - Officers (Folder 34.75)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.76)
    - Spanish, 1928-1930
      - Conferences (Folder 34.77)
      - Officers (Folder 34.78)
      - Officers (Folder 34.79)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.80)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.81)
    - Warden's Office, 1928-1930
      - Officers (Folder 34.82)
      - Officers (Folder 34.83)
      - Reports (Folder 34.84)
      - Conferences (Folder 34.85)
      - Officers (Folder 34.86)
      - Officers (Folder 34.87)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 34.88)
    - Zoology, 1928-1930
      - Officers (Folder 34.89)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.90)
      - Officers (Folder 34.91)
      - Appointments (Folder 34.92)
      - Conferences (Folder 34.93)
  - FACULTY, 1930-1932
    - General, 1930-1932
      - Faculty Bibliographies, 1930 - 1931 (Folder 35.1)
      - Faculty Bibliographies, 1931 - 1932 (Folder 35.2)
    - Admissions Committee, 1930-1932
      - Appointments (Folder 35.3)
      - Conferences (Folder 35.4)
      - Officers (Folder 35.5)
      - Officers (Folder 35.6)
    - Dean, 1930-1932
      - Appointments (Folder 35.7)
      - Conferences (Folder 35.8)
      - Reports (Folder 35.9)
      - Officers (Folder 35.10)
      - Officers (Folder 35.11)
    - Library, 1930-1932
      - Appointments (Folder 35.12)
      - Officers (Folder 35.13)
      - Officers (Folder 35.14)
    - Art, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 35.15)
      - Appointments (Folder 35.16)
      - Conferences (Folder 35.17)
      - Officers (Folder 35.18)
      - Officers (Folder 35.19)
      - Landscape Architecture (proposed major) (Folder 35.20)
    - Astronomy, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 35.21)
      - Appointments (Folder 35.22)
      - Conferences (Folder 35.23)
      - Officers (Folder 35.24)
    - Chemistry, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 35.25)
      - Appointments (Folder 35.26)
      - Conferences (Folder 35.27)
      - Officers (Folder 35.28)
    - Child Study, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 35.29)
      - Appointments (Folder 35.30)
      - Conferences (Folder 35.31)
      - Officers (Folder 35.32)
      - Officers (Folder 35.33)
    - Economics, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 35.34)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 35.35)
      - Appointments (Folder 35.36)
      - Conferences (Folder 35.37)
      - Officers (Folder 35.38)
    - Euthenics, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 35.39)
      - Conferences (Folder 35.40)
      - Officers (Folder 35.41)
      - Officers (Folder 35.42)
      - Crafts (Folder 35.43)
      - Summer School of Euthenics (Folder 35.44)
      - Summer School of Euthenics (Folder 35.45)
    - English, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 35.46)
      - Conferences (Folder 35.47)
      - Officers (Folder 35.48)
      - Officers (Folder 35.49)
      - Appointments (Folder 35.50)
      - Appointments (Folder 35.51)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 35.52)
      - Conferences (Folder 35.53)
      - Officers (Folder 35.54)
      - Officers (Folder 35.55)
      - Dramatic Productions (Folder 35.56)
    - French, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 35.57)
      - Appointments (Folder 35.58)
      - Conferences (Folder 35.59)
      - Officers (Folder 35.60)
    - Geology, 1930-1932
      - Conferences (Folder 35.61)
      - Officers (Folder 35.62)
    - German, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 35.63)
      - Appointments (Folder 35.64)
      - Conferences (Folder 35.65)
      - Officers (Folder 35.66)
    - Greek, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 35.67)
      - Officers (Folder 35.68)
    - Health, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 35.69)
      - Appointments (Folder 35.70)
      - Conferences (Folder 35.71)
      - Officers (Folder 35.72)
      - Mr. Calver (Folder 35.73)
      - Mr. Calver (Folder 35.74)
    - History, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 36.1)
      - Appointments (Folder 36.2)
      - Conferences (Folder 36.3)
      - Officers (Folder 36.4)
      - Officers (Folder 36.5)
    - Italian, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 36.6)
      - Appointments (Folder 36.7)
      - Conferences (Folder 36.8)
      - Officers (Folder 36.9)
      - Officers (Folder 36.10)
      - Roselli Resignation (Folder 36.11)
    - Latin, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 36.12)
      - Appointments (Folder 36.13)
      - Officers (Folder 36.14)
    - Mathematics, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 36.15)
      - Appointments (Folder 36.16)
      - Conferences (Folder 36.17)
      - Officers (Folder 36.18)
    - Music, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 36.19)
      - Appointments (Folder 36.20)
      - Conferences (Folder 36.21)
      - Officers (Folder 36.22)
      - Officers (Folder 36.23)
    - Philosophy, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 36.24)
      - Appointments (Folder 36.25)
      - Officers (Folder 36.26)
    - Physical Education, 1930-1932
      - Appointments (Folder 36.27)
      - Conferences (Folder 36.28)
      - Officers (Folder 36.29)
    - Physics, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 36.30)
      - Conferences (Folder 36.31)
      - Officers (Folder 36.32)
    - Physiology, 1930-1932
      - Appointments (Folder 36.33)
      - Conferences (Folder 36.34)
      - Officers (Folder 36.35)
    - Political Science, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 36.36)
      - Conferences (Folder 36.37)
      - Officers (Folder 36.38)
    - Psychology, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 36.39)
      - Conferences (Folder 36.40)
      - Officers (Folder 36.41)
    - Religion, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 36.42)
      - Appointments (Folder 36.43)
      - Conferences (Folder 36.44)
      - Officers (Folder 36.45)
    - Spanish, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 36.46)
      - Appointments (Folder 36.47)
      - Conferences (Folder 36.48)
      - Officers (Folder 36.49)
    - Warden's Office, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 36.50)
      - Appointments (Folder 36.51)
      - Conferences (Folder 36.52)
      - Officers (Folder 36.53)
      - Officers (Folder 36.54)
      - Reports (Folder 36.55)
      - Personnel Research Bureau (Folder 36.56)
      - Vocational Bureau (Folder 36.57)
    - Board of Residents, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 36.58)
      - Appointments (Folder 36.59)
      - Officers (Folder 36.60)
    - Zoology, 1930-1932
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 36.61)
      - Appointments (Folder 36.62)
      - Conferences (Folder 36.63)
      - Officers (Folder 36.64)
  - FACULTY, 1932-1934
    - General, 1932-1934
      - Faculty Bibliographies, 1933-1934 (Folder 36.65)
      - Faculty Secretary (Folder 36.66)
      - Faculty Science Club (Folder 36.67)
      - Chairmen of Departments (Folder 36.68)
      - Advisory Committee (Folder 36.69)
      - Committee on Committees (Folder 36.70)
      - Committee on Commencement (Folder 36.71)
      - Convocation Committee (Folder 36.72)
      - Curriculum Committee (Folder 36.73)
      - Curriculum Committee (Folder 36.74)
      - Committee on Euthenics (Folder 36.75)
      - Committee on Fellowships (Folder 36.76)
      - Committee on Foreign Study (Folder 36.77)
      - Founder's Day Committee (Folder 36.78)
      - Committee on Health (Folder 36.79)
      - Joint Committee (Folder 36.80)
      - Library Committee (Folder 36.81)
      - Committee on Research (Folder 36.82)
      - Schedule Committee (Folder 36.83)
      - Scholarship Committee (Folder 36.84)
      - Scholarship Committee (Folder 36.85)
      - Scholarship Committee (Folder 36.86)
      - Science Discussion Group (Folder 37.1)
      - Committee on Student Records (Folder 37.2)
      - Committee on Unemployment in Poughkeepsie (Folder 37.3)
    - Art, 1932 -1934
      - Officers (Folder 37.4)
      - Officers (Folder 37.5)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 37.6)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.7)
      - Appointments (Folder 37.8)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 37.9)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.10)
    - Astronomy, 1932 -1934
      - Officers (Folder 37.11)
      - Officers (Folder 37.12)
      - Appointments (Folder 37.13)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.14)
    - Botany, 1932-1934
      - Officers (Folder 37.15)
      - Appointments (Folder 37.16)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 37.17)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.18)
      - Officers (Folder 37.19)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 37.20)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.21)
      - Officers (Folder 37.22)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 37.23)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.24)
      - Appointments (Folder 37.25)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.26)
      - Botany Situation (Folder 37.27)
    - Chemistry,1932-1934
      - Officers (Folder 37.28)
      - Appointments (Folder 37.29)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 37.30)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.31)
      - Officers (Folder 37.32)
      - Appointments (Folder 37.33)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.34)
    - Child Study, 1932-1934
      - Officers (Folder 37.35)
      - Appointments (Folder 37.36)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.37)
      - Officers (Folder 37.38)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.39)
      - Appointments (Folder 37.40)
    - Dean, 1932-1934
      - Officers - Committee on Admission (Folder 37.41)
      - Officers (Folder 37.42)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.43)
      - Reports (Folder 37.44)
      - Officers - Board of Residents (Folder 37.45)
      - Appointments - Board of Residents (Folder 37.46)
      - Personnel Bureau (Folder 37.47)
      - Vocational Bureau (Folder 37.48)
      - Officers - Committee on Admission (Folder 37.49)
      - Officers (Folder 37.50)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.51)
      - Officers - Board of Residents (Folder 37.52)
      - Appointments - Board of Residents (Folder 37.53)
      - Personnel Bureau (Folder 37.54)
      - Vocational Bureau (Folder 37.55)
    - Economics, 1932-1934
      - Officers (Folder 37.56)
      - Officers (Folder 37.57)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 37.58)
      - Appointments (Folder 37.59)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.60)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 37.61)
      - Appointments (Folder 37.62)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.63)
    - English, 1932-1934
      - Appointments (Folder 37.64)
      - Officers (Folder 37.65)
      - Officers (Folder 37.66)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.67)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 37.68)
      - Officers (Folder 37.69)
      - Officers (Folder 37.70)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 37.71)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.72)
    - Euthenics, 1932-1934
      - Officers (Folder 37.73)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.74)
      - Summer Institute of Euthenics (Folder 37.75)
      - Officers (Folder 37.76)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.77)
      - Summer Institute (Folder 37.78)
    - French, 1932-1934
      - Officers (Folder 37.79)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 37.80)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.81)
      - Officers (Folder 37.82)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 37.83)
      - Conferences (Folder 37.84)
      - Appointments (Folder 37.85)
    - Geology, 1932-1934
      - Officers, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.1)
      - Applications and Recommendations, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.2)
      - Conferences, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.3)
      - Officers, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.4)
      - Appointments, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.5)
      - Applications and Recommendations, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.6)
      - Conferences, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.7)
    - German, 1932-1934
      - Officers, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.8)
      - Applications and Recommendations, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.9)
      - Conferences, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.10)
      - Appointments, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.11)
      - Officers, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.12)
      - Applications and Recommendations, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.13)
      - Conferences, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.14)
      - Appointments, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.15)
    - Greek, 1932-1934
      - Officers, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.16)
      - Conferences, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.17)
      - Officers, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.18)
    - Health, 1932-1934
      - Officers, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.19)
      - Applications and Recommendations, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.20)
      - Appointments, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.21)
      - Conferences, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.22)
      - Officers, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.23)
      - Applications and Recommendations, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.24)
      - Conferences, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.25)
    - History, 1932-1934
      - Officers, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.26)
      - Applications and Recommendations, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.27)
      - Officers, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.28)
      - Applications and Recommendations, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.29)
      - Appointments, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.30)
      - Conferences, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.31)
    - Italian, 1932-1934
      - Officers, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.32)
      - Conferences, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.33)
      - Appointments, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.34)
      - Officers, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.35)
      - Appointments, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.36)
      - Conferences, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.37)
    - Latin, 1932-1934
      - Officers, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.38)
      - Conferences, 1932-1933 (Folder 38.39)
      - Officers, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.40)
      - Applications and Recommendations, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.41)
      - Conferences, 1933-1934 (Folder 38.42)
    - Library, 1932-1934